tv-dome.net 2011-10-08

# Privacy Policy - TV Dome

## Privacy Policy:

TV-Dome.net is committed to protecting your privacy. TV-Dome.net does not sell, trade or rent your personal information to other companies. TV-Dome.net will not collect any personal information about you except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information.

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by TV-Dome.net.  If you do not agree with any of the terms of this policy, please do not use our Site. We reserve the right to change this policy at any time, and will post any changes to this policy when they go into effect. All changes will be posted on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Currently, TV-Dome.net provides aggregate statistics about our traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personal identifying information.

**1\. Ad-Serving**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.  
* Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads based on your visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.  
* You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
